Logan Thomas

Senior Associate Data Scientist Born 1989 in Mountain View, CA



About me

I'm a highly motivated and naturally curious individual with 6 years of experience using data science & machine learning techniques. I exhibit an analytical and detail-oriented nature, while placing strong value on building relationships.

Skills



Contact

6749 Catania Loop

✓ logan.thomas005@gmail.com

(321) 961-9107

in logan-thomas

loganthomas

Experience

Senior Associate Data Scientist I

Protection Engineering Consultants Austin, TX Aug 2020 - Present Advanced Technology & Research Team

Course Instructor

DataCamp Austin, TX Feb 2019 - Present

Lead Data Scientist

Nielsen Austin, TX Oct 2018 - Aug 2019 Machine Learning & Algorithms Team

Senior Data Scientist

Nielsen San Francisco, CA Aug 2016 - Oct 2018 **Digital Product Team**

Education

University of Florida

Master of Science in Mechanical Engineering 2012 - 2014 Minor in Statistics

Palm Beach Atlantic University

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics 2008 - 2012 Minor in Biblical Studies; Graduated Summa Cum Laude

Projects

turkey-bowl python-practice repo-scrape Python Python Python GitHub metadata Thanksgiving tradition -Collection of personal Mock NFL fantasy scraping (Hacktoberfest). Python notes, challenges, football draft. and scripts.

Contributions

pyjanitor

deap

Pythonic API for elligant data cleaning and method Algorithms in Python. chaining rountines on pandas DataFrames. https://github.com/ericmj I/pyjanitor

deap

Python package to define, **Distributed Evolutionary** measure.

pint

operate and manipultae https://github.com/DEAP/ physical quantities - the product of a numerical value and a unit of https://github.com/hgrec co/pint